Hello guys welcome to another video of stock
market friends, the
December quarter
results have been out from ICICI Lombard General Insurance, we will cover it in today's video,
friends let's
start the video, the audited financial
results of the quarter nine
months' date have been out, which we will cover and guys, the unaudited
financial results from the company and we
will analyse the results here and which
results numbers have been given, if we talk about them then the
numbers have been given in lakhs, this time the
total income revenue from operations, that is, the
premium earned this time, this time the
total gross premium is written,
if we look at it sorry if we talk about the total income, then the
premium earned by the company was a
net premium of 6474 crores, and
after this the gross premium is written and if
we talk about the gross premium
return of the company, the net premium return was 84
crores, premium earned was 5045 crores,
income from investment was 839 crores
And if we talk about the last quarter, then a
premium of Rs 5025 crore was earned
and in the last year a premium of Rs 4304 crore was earned
which has been quarter on
quarter year on year. The premium earned of both has been
seen increasing. The
total income after which was Rs 5800
crore in the last quarter and Rs
58.6 crore in the last year. The
total income was Rs 5004 crore. There is an increase in quarter on quarter
but the expense has also increased year on year. The
total expense of the company is around Rs
51974 crore in the last quarter and Rs 5186 crore
in the last year. The
total expense was Rs 4588 crore in the quarter on
quarter and it also increased in year on year
but the underwriting company incurred a loss
because the expense was more than the income
and this happened because an outstanding claim was made
which was Rs 11.6 crore due to which the company has a
loss, this is underwriting loss.  There is an
underwriting loss of Rs 152.5 crore in the last quarter and Rs 16.9 crore in the last year and Rs 2834 crore in the last year. It is
seen recovering quarter on quarter year on year. The
profit loss which happened here was transferred to the account of Rs
685 crore and after which the company got a
transfer of Rs 685 crore from the policy holders' funds which I told has been
transferred to the profit loss account and
apart from that there has been an income of Rs
276 crore from investment after which the profit of the company has come out. If you look at the
total here, the
last quarter profit is Rs 724.3 crore, last
quarter profit is Rs 69.9 crore, last
profit is Rs 431 crore, quarter on quarter
year on year, the EPS has increased quarter on quarter year on year,
last quarter EPS is Rs 14.48, last quarter
EPS is Rs 13.8, last year EPS is Rs 8.73, it is
seen increasing quarter on quarter year on year.
Here the result of the guys company is
of a very strong page, be it quarter on
quarter  Or year on year
both income and profit are seen increasing.
If we look at the revenue here, the
profit which was 665 sorry 635
crores was expected to be generated
but guys the company has generated a better profit than that and the
revenue which was guys, a
profit of around 5500 a 72 crores
was expected to be generated and this was also beaten, meaning that the overall
company is seen doing market estimator.
If we
talk about its shares, if we look at the company's shares here, it
closed at ₹1 1955, there was a
profit of 2.5 per cent, profit of 4.4 per cent in five days,
profit of 2 per cent is being seen in one month,
so now we are
ending the video here, if you have any
doubt ask in the comment box, we will meet
in the next day till then bye bye